perfectmemorials.com 2007-10-09

# Privacy & Security - Perfect Memorials

Perfect Memorials knows that you care how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our privacy policy. By visiting Perfect Memorials, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy & Security Notice.

### What Personal Information About Customers Does Perfect Memorials Gather?

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and continually improve your shopping experience at Perfect Memorials. Here are the types of information we gather. 

  * **Information You Give Us:** We receive and store any information you enter on our Web site or give us in any other way. We use the information that you provide for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, improving our stores, and communicating with you. 
  * **Automatic Information:** We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. For example, like many Web sites, we use "cookies," and we obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses Perfect Memorials. 
  * **E-mail Communications:** If you do not want to receive e-mail or other mail from us, please adjust your [Your Profile Preferences](https://www.perfectmemorials.com/account.php). 
  * **Information from Other Sources:** We might receive information about you from other sources and add it to our account information. 

### What About Cookies?

  * Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our systems to recognize your browser. 

### Does Perfect Memorials Share the Information It Receives?

Information about our customers is an important part of our business, and **we are not in the business of selling it to others**. We share customer information only as described below and with subsidiaries Perfect Memorials LLC controls that either are subject to this Privacy Notice or follow practices at least as protective as those described in this Privacy Notice. 

  * **Agents:** We employ other companies and individuals to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include fulfilling orders, delivering packages, sending postal mail and e-mail, removing repetitive information from customer lists, analyzing data, providing marketing assistance, providing search results and links (including paid listings and links), processing credit card payments, and providing customer service. They have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for other purposes. 
  * **Protection of Perfect Memorials and Others:** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our [Conditions of Use](http://www.perfectmemorials.com/conditions.php) and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of Perfect Memorials, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. Obviously, however, this does not include selling, renting, sharing, or otherwise disclosing personally identifiable information from customers for commercial purposes in violation of the commitments set forth in this Privacy Notice. 
  * **With Your Consent:** Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information. 

### How Secure Is Information About Me?

  * We work to protect the security of your information during transmission by using Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, which encrypts information you input. 
  * We reveal only limited digits of your credit card numbers when confirming an order. Of course, we transmit the entire credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. 
  * It is important for you to protect against unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to sign off when finished using a shared computer. 

### Which Information Can I Access?

Perfect Memorials gives you access to a broad range of information about your account and your interactions with Perfect Memorials for the limited purpose of viewing and, in certain cases, updating that information. 

### Conditions of Use, Notices, and Revisions

If you choose to visit Perfect Memorials, your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Notice, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of the law of the state of Minnesota . If you have any concern about privacy at Perfect Memorials, please [contact us](http://www.perfectmemorials.com/contact_us.php) with a thorough description, and we will try to resolve it. 

Our business changes constantly, and our Privacy Notice will change also. We may e-mail periodic reminders of our notices and conditions, unless you have instructed us not to, but you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes. Unless stated otherwise, our current Privacy Notice applies to all information that we have about you and your account. We stand behind the promises we make, however, and will never materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers. 

### Information You Give Us

You provide most such information when you search, buy, answer a questionnaire, or communicate with customer service. For example, you provide information when you search for a product; place an order through Perfect Memorials or one of our third-party sellers; provide information in [ Your Account](https://www.perfectmemorials.com/login.php); communicate with us by phone, e-mail, or otherwise; complete a questionnaire; and employ other Personal Notification Services, such as Available to Order Notifications. As a result of those actions, you might supply us with such information as your name, address, and phone numbers; credit card information; people to whom purchases have been shipped, including addresses and phone number; people (with addresses and phone numbers).

### Automatic Information

Examples of the information we collect and analyze include the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the Internet; login; e-mail address; password; computer and connection information such as browser type and version, operating system, and platform; purchase history; the full Uniform Resource Locator (URL) clickstream to, through, and from our Web site, including date and time; cookie number; products you viewed or searched for; and the phone number you used to call our 800 number. During some visits we may use software tools such as JavaScript to measure and collect session information, including page response times, download errors, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information (such as scrolling, clicks, and mouse-overs), and methods used to browse away from the page. 

### Information from Other Sources

Examples of information we receive from other sources include updated delivery and address information from our carriers or other third parties, which we use to correct our records and deliver your next purchase or communication more easily; account information, purchase or redemption information; search term and search result information; search results and links, including paid listings (such as Sponsored Links from Google); and credit history information from credit bureaus, which we use to help prevent and detect fraud and to offer certain credit or financial services to some customers. 

### Information You Can Access

Examples of information you can access easily at Perfect Memorials include up-to-date information regarding recent orders; personally identifiable information (including name, e-mail, password, communications preferences, and address book); payment settings (including credit card information and gift certificates); and e-mail notification settings.

### Safe & Secure Online Transactions

Perfect Memorials is concerned about the safety and security of our customers. Accordingly, we have put a number of technological protections in place to ensure that our transaction process is extremely safe and that our customers' information is secure.
